With his newspaper. Lisbeth is in an upmarket tailors.
The tailor shows her a leather motorcycle jacket he's made
from a photo of Mikael wearing an identical garment.
She looks surprised by the tailor's comment.
Back at her apartment, she writes a card
which has a picture of a horse on it
and put it in an envelope.
She addresses the envelope to ‘M’.
Night.
Lisbeth rides her motorcycle down a cobbled street
with snow piled at the curbside.
She parks on a corner outside Mikael's apartment
and removes her crash helmet.
She takes a package from the back of the bike,
but stops dead when she sees Mikael
leave his apartment with Erika.
She watches numbly as the couple walk away
with their arms around each other.
Lisbeth looks down as Mikael and Erika
get into a waiting taxi.
Lisbeth turns away and flings the package which has the card
attached to it into a nearby dumpster.
She puts her crash helmet back on,
gets on her bike
and starts it up.
A solitary figure, she rides off into the night.